ehftv.com 2019-04-08

# 

                                                   Privacy Notice – EHF Marketing GmbH
                                                                      May 2018
1.        Introduction
1.        EHF Marketing GmbH respects your privacy and personal data. This Privacy Notice (hereinafter referred
          to as “Notice”) explains how we process your personal data when you register for our services and
          browse on our Website. Personal data means any information which allows EHF Marketing to directly or
          indirectly identify you.
1.1.      This Notice applies where EHF Marketing GmbH acts as a controller of the personal data being collected
          and processed from our Website. This means that this Notice applies where EHF Marketing GmbH
          determines the purposes and means of the processing of the personal data.
1.2.      The personal data collected and processed by EHF Marketing GmbH during your access to our Website
          will be processed in accordance with the EU General Data Protection Regulation (hereinafter referred to
          as the “GDPR”) and with any other applicable privacy and data protection laws.
1.3.      The EHF Marketing GmbH Website may contain links to websites of third-parties which are not covered
          by this privacy Notice. EHF Marketing GmbH does not accept any responsibilities or liabilities for third-
          party websites.
1.4.      We strongly encourage you to take some time to read this Notice in full. If you do not agree to this Notice,
          we kindly request you not to provide us with your personal data.
2.        Who is EHF Marketing GmbH?
2.1.      EHF Marketing is the marketing arm and subsidiary of the European Handball Federation. The company
          works closely with marketing and media partners, as well as with Europe’s leading clubs to realise the full
          potential of the sport on the international sports market. EHF Marketing GmbH is responsible for the
          marketing and media rights of club competitions including the VELUX EHF Champions League, WOMEN’S
          EHF Champions League and the Men’s EHF Cup.
3.        What Personal Data Do We Collect?
3.1.      When using EHF Marketing GmbH services, we may collect any information in which the services user can
          be identified. You can find below the personal data which we collect automatically, the personal data
          which is provided to us and the personal data which is collected from other sources.
3.2.      Automatically Collected Personal Data
3.2.1. In order to provide certain functionalities, when you access our Website, we may collect your IP address.
          In addition, we make use of cookies to better understand how you use our Website.
3.2.2. More information can be found in Section 4.1 and Section 6 of this Notice.
4.        How We Process Your Data?
                                            EHF Marketing GmbH, Hoffingergasse 18, 1120 Vienna, Austria
                            Tel: +43 1 80151 200 Fax: +43 1 80151 219 Email: handball@ehfmarketing.com Web: ehfmarketing.com
     FN 264635 w | HG Wien | Bank Austria, Am Hof 2, A-1010 Vienna, Austria | Bank code 12000 | Account number 51582 834 501 BIC/SWIFT BKAUATWW
                                                | IBAN AT69 1200 0515 8283 4501 | VAT No. ATU61835535

4.1.      For What Purposes Do We Process Your Personal Data?
There are several reason why we use your personal data. In the most cases, it is about measuring your behavior
on our Website and, based on that, create personalized experiences, both from a content as well as from an
advertising point of view. More specifically, the purposes are:
      For measuring on how users browse and behave on our Website
      For providing you with our content services such as newsletter service .
      For notifying you in case you participated in a prize game
      For serving personalized advertising to our users in order to increase the accuracy of our advertising
4.2.      On What Legal Grounds Do We Process Your Data?
          In order to process your personal data, we may rely on the different legal grounds, including:
4.2.1. Your consent, insofar as it is legally required or permitted. If we rely on your consent as a legal basis for
          processing your personal data, you may withdraw your consent at any time. This right is further specified
          in Section 13.9 of this Notice.
4.2.2. The necessity to establish a contractual relationship with you and to perform our obligations under the
          concerned contract.
4.2.3. The necessity for us to comply with legal obligations to establish, exercise, or defend ourselves from legal
          claims.
4.2.4. The necessity to pursue our legitimate interests, including, but not limited to:
4.2.4.1.       Improving the user experience and understanding how you behave on our Website
4.2.4.2.       Improving the security and performance of our Website
4.2.4.3.       To administer and generally conduct business within the Company
5.        Do We Collect Data From Children?
5.1.      EHF Marketing GmbH does not knowingly collect personal data from children. The definition of “children”
          is subject to local and national laws and may vary accordingly.
6.        How Do We Use Cookies And Other Tracking Technologies?
6.1.      EHF Marketing GmbH reserves the right to use so-called cookies. Cookies are alpha-numerical identifiers
          temporarily filed in the working memory ("Session Cookie") or permanently stored on the hard disk of the
          User's computer ("Permanent Cookie").
6.2.      Such information includes, but is not limited to, the User's IP address, login data, type and version of
          browser, the date and time when the User visits our Websites, and a cookie number.
6.3.      The use of cookies enables EHF Marketing GmbH to "recognize" the User at his/her next visit and to align
          the offer on the Websites with the User's interests. Cookies are generally deleted once the User logs out
          of his personal account, or cookies expire on their dates of expiration. So-called language cookies which
          "recognize" the language of the Website previously used when the User visits the Website are not deleted
          when the User logs out. If the User does not log out of his personal account, all cookies are deleted after
                                            EHF Marketing GmbH, Hoffingergasse 18, 1120 Vienna, Austria
                            Tel: +43 1 80151 200 Fax: +43 1 80151 219 Email: handball@ehfmarketing.com Web: ehfmarketing.com
     FN 264635 w | HG Wien | Bank Austria, Am Hof 2, A-1010 Vienna, Austria | Bank code 12000 | Account number 51582 834 501 BIC/SWIFT BKAUATWW
                                                | IBAN AT69 1200 0515 8283 4501 | VAT No. ATU61835535

          three months, at the latest.
6.4.      Withdrawal of Consent for the Use of 1st Party Cookies
6.4.1. At any time, users can delete their cookies from their browser through their browser settings.
          Additionally, EHF Marketing GmbH deletes all 1st party cookies automatically after 6 weeks of setting. This
          period of 6 weeks is renewed anytime you visit our Website.
6.4.2. The type of cookies we may place on your browser can be clustered in three groups:
         Functional Cookies
          We make use of these cookies to ensure a good experience when browsing on our Website.
         Analytics Cookies
          We make use of these cookies to measure user behavior.
         Marketing and Advertisement Cookies
          We work with advertisers and companies which helps us enable advertising on our Website. These
          companies may set certain cookies to understand your behavior and provide you with tailored
          advertising.
          You can find a list of all the cookies we place - both 1st and 3rd party cookies - on the following link.
7.        Withdrawal of Consent for the Use of Cookies
7.1.      You can opt-out from the use of marketing and analytics cookies by using the footer on our Website.
8.        Embedded Content and Share Links/Likes To Facebook, Twitter and Similar
8.1.      We may embed content from websites such as Facebook, Youtube, Twitter and similar on our Website.
          Pages with the embedded content may set cookies from the relevant website. We recommend that you
          check the relevant website for more information.
8.2.      When you use one of the share buttons on our Website or when you click on buttons contained within
          the embedded content on our Website, such as “Facebook like buttons” a cookie may be set on your
          browser by the relevant third-party. EHF Marketing GmbH does not control the setting of these cookies
          and does not block the cookies from these websites. We recommend that you check the relevant website
          for more information.
9.        When Do We Transfer Your Personal Data?
9.1.      We may transfer your personal data to trusted third-parties located outside of the European Union. We
          may disclose your personal data to Sportradar Group companies located outside of the European Union.
9.2.      When transferring your personal data to a third-party located outside of the European Union or in
          countries which do not provide the same standard of personal data protection, we have put in place
          adequate measures to protect your data, such as organizational and legal measures (including the EU
          Model Contract Clauses) to ensure the protection of the personal data. You may obtain a copy of these
                                            EHF Marketing GmbH, Hoffingergasse 18, 1120 Vienna, Austria
                            Tel: +43 1 80151 200 Fax: +43 1 80151 219 Email: handball@ehfmarketing.com Web: ehfmarketing.com
     FN 264635 w | HG Wien | Bank Austria, Am Hof 2, A-1010 Vienna, Austria | Bank code 12000 | Account number 51582 834 501 BIC/SWIFT BKAUATWW
                                                | IBAN AT69 1200 0515 8283 4501 | VAT No. ATU61835535

         measures by contacting the Sportradar Privacy Office, which can be found below in Section 15 of this
         Notice.
10.      Who Do We Transfer Your Personal Data To?
10.1.    There are several trusted partners we work with that process the personal data we collect. The partners
         are clustered in the following categories:
   User Statistics And Website Analytics Companies
   Functional Cookies Companies
   Advertisers
11.      How Do We Secure Your Data?
11.1.    EHF Marketing GmbH uses all available technical and organizational security measures in order to protect
         your personal data against a breach of security leading to the accidental or unlawful destruction, loss,
         alteration, unauthorized disclosure of, or access to, your personal data transmitted, stored or otherwise
         processed.
11.2.    EHF Marketing GmbH employees are required to keep personal data confidential. EHF Marketing GmbH
         employees will only transfer your personal data to third parties as described in Section 6 and 7 of this
         Notice.
12.      How Long Is My Data Kept?
12.1.    EHF Marketing GmbH does not keep personal data for longer than it is necessary for the purposes set out
         in Section 2 of this Notice.
12.2.    For personal data that are not collected from cookies (see Section 3 of this Notice), we delete all personal
         data after 2 years of non-usage. That means, that if you have not logged in or have not consumed a
         service you have previously registered for a period of 2 years, we delete your personal data. We may
         actively contact you before we delete the data.
12.3.    For cookies, we delete all 1st party cookies (including your consent to use your personal data outside of
         functionalities that you actively have to register for) after 6 weeks of non-usage. That means, that if you
         have not visited our website for a period of more than 6 weeks, we delete all 1st party cookies.
12.4.
13.      What Are My Rights?
13.1.    EHF Marketing GmbH reserves the right to refuse to give effect to a petitioner’s request in the event that
         we are unable to ascertain your identity.
13.2.    Right to Access
13.2.1. You have the right to obtain from EHF Marketing GmbH a confirmation of whether EHF Marketing GmbH
         is processing your data. Should EHF Marketing GmbH process your data, you have the right to access your
         personal data and to obtain further information regarding the processing of your personal data.
                                           EHF Marketing GmbH, Hoffingergasse 18, 1120 Vienna, Austria
                           Tel: +43 1 80151 200 Fax: +43 1 80151 219 Email: handball@ehfmarketing.com Web: ehfmarketing.com
    FN 264635 w | HG Wien | Bank Austria, Am Hof 2, A-1010 Vienna, Austria | Bank code 12000 | Account number 51582 834 501 BIC/SWIFT BKAUATWW
                                               | IBAN AT69 1200 0515 8283 4501 | VAT No. ATU61835535

13.3.    Right to Rectification
13.3.1. You have the right to have your personal data rectified by EHF Marketing GmbH in the event that your
         personal data is inaccurate. You may also rectify the information by reviewing and changing the personal
         information on your account settings
13.4.    Right to Erasure
13.4.1. Under certain conditions, you have the right to have your personal data erased without delay. Those
         conditions are listed at article 17 of the GDPR.
13.5.    Right to Restriction of Processing
13.5.1. Under certain conditions, you have the right to restrict the processing of your personal data. Those
         conditions are listed at article 18 of the GDPR.
13.6.    Right to Object to Processing
13.6.1. Under certain conditions, you have the right to object to the processing of your personal data by EHF
         Marketing GmbH. Those conditions are listed at article 21 of the GDPR.
13.7.    Right to Data Portability
13.7.1. You have the right to obtain your personal data in a structured, commonly used machine-readable format
         and to have your personal data transferred to another controller upon your request, and where
         technically feasible insofar as the processing of your personal data relies on your consent or it is
         necessary for the performance of a contract between you and EHF Marketing GmbH
13.8.    Right to Complain To a Supervisory Authority
13.8.1. Should you believe that EHF Marketing GmbH has infringed the applicable data protection laws, you have
         the right to file a complaint before the concerned Data Protection Authority.
13.9.    Right to Withdraw Consent
13.9.1. You may withdraw your consent to the processing of your personal data insofar as the processing relies
         on your consent. This does not apply if the processing is required for the performance of a contract
         between EHF Marketing GmbH and you or if the processing is based on EHF Marketing GmbH legitimate
         interests.
14.      Policy Changes
14.1.    EHF Marketing GmbH reserves the right, at its discretion, to update, change, modify, add or amend this
         Policy by publishing a new version on our Website.
15.      Contact
15.1.    Should you have any questions regarding the processing of your personal data or should you wish to
         exercise a right as provided in Section of this Policy, please contact our Data Protection Officer at
                                           EHF Marketing GmbH, Hoffingergasse 18, 1120 Vienna, Austria
                           Tel: +43 1 80151 200 Fax: +43 1 80151 219 Email: handball@ehfmarketing.com Web: ehfmarketing.com
    FN 264635 w | HG Wien | Bank Austria, Am Hof 2, A-1010 Vienna, Austria | Bank code 12000 | Account number 51582 834 501 BIC/SWIFT BKAUATWW
                                               | IBAN AT69 1200 0515 8283 4501 | VAT No. ATU61835535

     handball@ehfmarketing.com
                                       EHF Marketing GmbH, Hoffingergasse 18, 1120 Vienna, Austria
                       Tel: +43 1 80151 200 Fax: +43 1 80151 219 Email: handball@ehfmarketing.com Web: ehfmarketing.com
FN 264635 w | HG Wien | Bank Austria, Am Hof 2, A-1010 Vienna, Austria | Bank code 12000 | Account number 51582 834 501 BIC/SWIFT BKAUATWW
                                           | IBAN AT69 1200 0515 8283 4501 | VAT No. ATU61835535
